Oh haha.
And today is the seventy-seven
thirty-five thousand.
For me it's a lot brother.
I still have to wear a pair of parades.
Is it on?
It's just that I can't bro.
She took me half the way there.
Workshop.
The gym sold Chevette.
Everything had a purpose in mind to raise some money to build something bigger.
Dude I managed to raise some good money but I still can't figure it out.
Vei I'm getting worried because the days are
passing and the business doesn't unfold.
That's it bro.
You have to give in the hand of God.
And we're going to go,
right? See
Of course I'm interested but Saturday Saturday I have
an event man what are you playing caraca mano?
Only if we go in the morning does it happen.
Go upstairs brother.
I don't have time anymore.
No
bir AZ.